FRANKLIN PETERS

PROGRAMMER AT TRC

Sept. 2021 - Dec. 2022

gagewaguespack@gmail.com 📞 (985)-718-7763 🗘 Gage-Waguespack

SUMMARY

Game Programmer with 3+ years of experience! I know how to program in C++, C#, Unity, and Unreal Engine—looking to expand my programming knowledge and gain more experience in the field working on just about any project. Great team member and very flexible with hours, pay, and type of work.

I'm a hardworking employee who tends to work by the books, I very much dislike constant changes in policy and procedure and enjoy a steady workflow throughout the day with minimal breaks unless needed.

I have experience down stacking pallets from trucks, stocking, fronting products to shelves, cooler organization, produce display organization, serving food, bussing tables, and cleaning up hardwood floors, carpets, shelves, etc.

I do have GAD and IBS but I am open to discussing what is going on and how I am doing throughout my shifts. I prefer open communication and can be very understanding when things need to be done. I have a one-track mind and tend to complete my tasks in a quick and orderly manner before double-checking everything and moving on.

EDUCATION

Slidell High School Jan. 2016 - June 2018

St. James High School Aug. 2018 - June 2020

High School Graduate 2020

I transferred from Slidell High to St. James in 2018.

Academy of Interactive Entertainment Aug. 2020 - June 2022

Associates of Occupational Studies and Game Programming 2022

EMPLOYMENT

Rouses, Produce Clerk, Lafayette, LA Jan. 2024 - Mar. 2024

Down stacked pallets of fresh produce and organized as well as date them whilst putting them in the cooler. Also culled the department of old produce.

TRC, Programmer, Home Dec. 2022 - Apr. 2024

Programmer, App and Game Tester, and also worked with feedback to update apps.

Chick-Fil-A, Staff Member, Lafayette, LA

Worked both in the kitchen and with the customers.

Olive Garden, Busser, Lafayette, LA 2020 - 2021

Cleaned Tables and occasionally assisted customers as well as stocked and refilled soda machines, tea, and coffee.

SKILLS

GAME PROGRAMMING: C++, C#, Markdown

TEAM WORK: Training others at CFA, Working with others on company projects.

SOFTWARE AND TOOLS: Microsoft Visual Studios, Unreal Engine, Unity, Git, Perforce, Trello, Plastic

PROJECTS

Item Generation Spring 2021 - Jan. 2022

A project with a complex game system that allows you to randomly generate weapons! (can be used in bigger projects)

Stratus Jan. 2022 - June 2022

Our major production project at AIE in which we made, pitched, and produced a game to Itch.io with trailers and documentation!